# Bryan Schneller

# Full-Stack Web Developer

730 Branniff Dr.
Cary, NC 27513
(484) 894-4578
bryan.schneller@gmail.com
https://bryanschnellerwebdev.netlify.app/

## **OVERVIEW**

I am an efficient and creative programmer with a strong vision for marketable product development. I am excited to bring my talents and interests to a dynamic team. Eight years of experience in the brain injury rehabilitation field have strengthened my organizational, communication, and interpersonal skills. I enjoy the consistent challenge and considerable rewards of contributing to the internet which I regard as a fascinating achievement of humankind that brings profound opportunities for connection.

#### **SKILLS**

I have experience building unique and effective full-stack web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB and Mongoose, PostGreSQL and Sequelize, and using Git and Github and the agile framework in a team project development setting.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Wegmans, Cary, NC - Cashier (part-time)

AUG 2023 - PRESENT

- Provide a positive customer experience with thoughtful, individualized service
- Dynamically organize items for efficient and optimal bagging while handling cash transactions

#### UNC Full-Stack Web Development Course, Chapel Hill, NC

NOV 2023 - May 2024

Accelerated program focused on independent coding and team project-management skills in technologies including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Express.js, Handlebars, React, Node.js, SQL and NoSQL databases, MERN stack, Git, Github, and the Agile development framework

Community Partnerships, Inc., Raleigh, NC - Rehabilitation Specialist

OCT 2022 - JUNE 2023

- Administered formal and informal assessments to create a treatment plan in order to prepare individuals for employment and independence
- Implemented person-centered treatment plans and carried out therapy sessions to address needs relating to cognitive rehabilitation, therapy and counseling, case management, and occupational preparation
- Schedule sessions and create plans to track and report treatment outcomes

Success Rehabilitation, Inc., Quakertown, PA - Cognitive Rehabilitation Specialist

FEB 2017 - SEPT 2022

- Administered standardized assessments and evaluations to determine individual strengths, weaknesses, and potential strategies
- Developed and implemented individualized treatment programs to address identified needs
- Functioned as on-call administrator to address staffing and maintenance issues and perform company-wide communications as needed

## **EDUCATION**

**University of Pittsburgh, PA** - Bachelor's of Science, Psychology (Cum Laude) SEP 2009 - MAY 2013

Solid academic foundation in the study of psychology including research methods, and biological, cognitive, and neuroscience aspects